Let us start with the another executable called a 32.exe, it was called as a log base.
So the 32.exe will be one of the important process, important windows in general that was handling
those certificates.
So, your machine has a lot of applications that it has been running and the operating
system was running.
So, the operating system and that has different different certificates, right?
So, digital certificate or whatever you can call.
So, we have maybe some of some know the digital certificates and all.
So, the operating system also have some certificates, it is used to handle this certificate
and all.
So, this is responsible for like downloading or importing, exporting the certificates and
verifying the certificate.
So, the threat actors will use to those certificates to download a malicious files into
the machine, ok.
So, probably they will be using the strings like this, so you will, you are all cache,
threat dot, flash, dash shift, and they will give the server with the malware, ok.
So, if you are placing your own malware in your server, so they will be giving, given the
URL here and they will save the malware and fill the machine, ok.
So, they do not need to use any Chrome.exe or Firefox.exe, so absolutely you can't able
to use that kind of executable when you are inside the machine because there will be no
options using that, ok.
Some machines they have a Chrome, some machine, there will be a message and some machine
that will be missing.
So, you have to completely relay on other techniques, so if you want to download anything
from the internet, ok.
So, you can use a certificate already if you do download something from a remote server and
you can save it in the machine, ok.
So, this was particularly handled by the, this, certainly will be handling the certificates
on it, it will be, I already said it is going to download a certificate from the certificate
authority server, so we are using the certificate, so our malicious server, ok.
You can download anything, also it is used to encode and decode, ok, so we can use it
for encoding and decoding, so like this and like this, so I will give a little bit example,
so how the threat activity will be going to download the malware files, ok.
So, because most of the instance which I have faced, they are using this techniques to download
the malicious files into the machine, ok.
Let us get on to the machine and let us close this window, close the PBR, close it, let
go to the M assets, ok.
So, let us load something like, for which file we can download, let us see, we will download
the memicats, ok and we can save it in, in, instead of a machine, ok, memicats, get up,
this is one of the malicious files, the memicats, let us go to the X64, here this memicats
study and see, let us copy this, ok, so we are going to use this 30-dill split F, right,
you are a cache split dash F, let us use the CMD, you are T, U, T, U, R, L, catch, split dash
F, so you have to save this file as a memicats, let us execute this, so now you can see
it is an R9 and it is saying the 30-dill URL cache command has been complete, turn successfully,
let us do DAR, ok, so you can see the files here, it was memicats, previous which you
have downloaded from the 30-dill.exe, so you can, it was downloaded 8 to T, you can see
my time, and this is the beta of 298,00050, so the file has been downloaded successfully,
so this is the way that the attacker will use to download at that particular device from
their servers, so instead of giving the GitHub here, they will be using their own server
HTTPS like, let me hack our server, last malware.ex, so they will use this techniques to download
the file and put it in the inside of it, ok, so this will be easily await the Angular
software and EDR platform, because the 30-dill response will be handling the certificates,
this is the antivirus software, so EDR blog, the 30-dill.exe, so now you are operating
system and you cannot be able to update anything, ok, because the operating system needs
30-dill.exe for some updates and all, ok, so the static detection and dynamic detection
that was not possible in this side, only they can go for a behavioral based detections,
ok, so let us go up to this video and we will continue our discussion in our next video,
see you guys, bye bye.